NADIA LÓPEZ

QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER

Contact Person

(+52) 55 49 35 90 49



nbla.escom@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/i n/nadia-lopez-aguilar



nadia-lopez.com

Education

B.S in Computer Systems Engineering

National Polytechnic Institute | Mexico

Associate Degree in Programming

National Polytechnic Institute | Mexico

Languages

Spanish

English

Technologies

TESTING

JUnit

- Cypress
- Postman

Cucumber

REPORTING

- Jira
- Slack
- Zephyr
- Confluence

DEVELOPMENT

Java

- React
- MySQL
- Node.js

OPERATIONS

- Git
- Jenkins
- Grafana
- GCP Logs

About me

I am a dedicated and responsible QA engineer with 3+ years of experience and a passion for growth and continuous learning in the technology sector. I'm looking for an opportunity to enhance my knowledge while contributing to the quality and success of a product.

Job Experience

October 2023 - Present

SDET

BetterCloud

- Defined and implemented the test strategy for a team in a SaaS application management company.
- Developed and crafted detailed test plans and test cases aligned with the product team's requirements.
- · Created, maintained, and optimized end-to-end automated test suites.
- · Led the migration and development of back-end integration tests
- · Performed exploratory testing

October 2021 - May 2023

QA ENGINEER

Kandy - AVC technologies

- Reported and documented testing result reports and tracked bug tickets.
- Created and monitored smoke. regression, and sanity tests.
- Designed and developed API test scripts for automated validations in a CI/CD environment.
- Conducted test plans and test case reviews.

January 2021 - June 2021

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Liberato Software

- Designed developed UI and components and back-end services.
- · Created component unit tests and integration tests.